// src/data/accordionData.js

const AccordionData = {
    onlineConsultation: [
        {
            id: "1",
            question: "Access Doctors via Call or Video",
            answer: "Conveniently connect from the comfort of your home or office.",
          },
          {
            id: "2",
            question: "Consult with Top Doctors",
            answer: "Choose from 30+ specialist doctors across various fields.",
          },
          {
            id: "3",
            question: "Digital Prescription",
            answer: "Get lifetime access to your prescriptions, along with reminders for follow-up consultations.",
          },
    ],
    inClinicConsultation: [
        {
            id: "1",
            question: "Access Leading Doctors at the Clinic of Your Choice",
            answer: "Visit any clinic or hospital nationwide.",
          },
          {
            id: "2",
            question: "Consult with Top Specialists",
            answer: "All medical specialties are included.",
          },
          {
            id: "3",
            question: "Choose Allopathic, Ayurvedic, or Homeopathic Doctors",
            answer: "Consult with your preferred doctors, no matter their practice.",
          },
    ],
    diagnostics: [
        {
            id: "1",
            question: "Choose Allopathic, Ayurvedic, or Homeopathic Doctors.",
            answer: "Locate and book diagnostic tests at trusted facilities close to you.",
          },
          {
            id: "2",
            question: "Quick and Easy Booking",
            answer: "Schedule tests online or offline at your convenience with flexible appointment options.",
          },
          {
            id: "3",
            question: "Fast Results",
            answer: "Get your test results quickly, accompanied by clear and actionable insights for review.",
          },
    ],
    pharmacy: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Order pharmacy Anytime, anywhere in India",
        answer: "Order medicine from OPDSure's partners or trusted pharmacies at your convenience.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Home Delivery Available",
        answer: "Place an online order for home delivery from trusted pharmacy brands, right to your doorstep.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Easy Prescription Management",
        answer: "Easily order medications and manage your prescriptions with just a few clicks.",
      },
    ],
    claimProcess: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Fast and Simple Claims",
        answer: "Submit your claims quickly with an intuitive, user-friendly platform.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Instant Status Updates",
        answer: "Track your claim's progress in real-time with immediate notifications.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Effortless Settlements",
        answer: "Enjoy smooth, swift claim settlements directly into your account.",
      },
    ],
    healthCard: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Personlised Health Card",
        answer: "Easy and Quick Pay your doctor consultation bills at the counter.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Accepted at top clinics and hospitals.",
        answer: "Gain access to doctors nationwide across India.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Convenient Access",
        answer: "Manage and use your health card easily through a mobile app or online portal.",
      },
    ],
    healthCheckups: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Complimentary Health Checkups",
        answer: "Complimentary health checkups with every plan.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Convenient Scheduling",
        answer: "Book check-ups at times that work for you, with flexible online or in-clinic options.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Detailed Reports",
        answer: "Receive clear, actionable health reports to guide your wellness decisions and follow-up care.",
      },
    ],
    ambulance: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Immediate Response",
        answer: "Get rapid emergency transportation with our 24/7 ambulance service.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Advanced Medical Support",
        answer: "Equipped with top-notch medical equipment and trained personnel for optimal care.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Real-Time Tracking",
        answer: "Monitor the ambulance's location and arrival time with our live tracking feature.",
      },
    ],
    gymFitness: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Tailored Workout Plans",
        answer: "Access customized fitness programs to match your goals and abilities.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Flexible Membership Options",
        answer: "Choose from a variety of membership plans that fit your schedule and budget.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Expert Trainers and Classes",
        answer: "Benefit from professional guidance and diverse classes for all fitness levels.",
      },
    ],
    mentalWellness: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Personalized Counseling",
        answer: "Access tailored therapy and counseling services to address your unique needs.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "24/7 Support",
        answer: "Benefit from round-the-clock access to mental health resources and helplines.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Mindfulness and Stress Relief",
        answer: "Engage in guided sessions and tools for effective stress management and emotional well-being.",
      },
    ],
    specialEducation: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Customized Learning Plans",
        answer: "Receive tailored educational strategies to support individual learning needs and goals.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Expert Educators",
        answer: "Work with qualified professionals skilled in special education techniques and support.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Inclusive Resources",
        answer: "Access a range of specialized tools and materials designed to enhance learning experiences.",
      },
    ],
    vaccinations: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Easy Appointment Booking",
        answer: "Schedule your vaccination quickly and effortlessly online or at local clinics.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Wide Range of Vaccines",
        answer: "Access essential vaccines for flu, travel, and routine immunizations, all in one place.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Safe and Efficient",
        answer: "Receive your vaccines in a clean, professional setting with minimal wait times.",
      },
    ],
    yoga: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Personalized Yoga Sessions",
        answer: "Enjoy customized classes tailored to your fitness level and wellness goals.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Flexible Class Options",
        answer: "Choose from a variety of online or in-person classes to fit your schedule.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Expert Instructors",
        answer: "Practice with skilled instructors who guide you through effective techniques and postures.",
      },
    ],
  };
  
  export default AccordionData;
  